<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<website>
    <index>
        <title>Welcome to Our Website</title>
        <content>
            <p>Welcome to our website. This is the homepage where you can find links to various topics we cover.</p>
            <p>Explore the following sections:</p>
            <ul>
                <li><a href="index.html">Home</a></li>
                <li><a href="topic1.html">Topic 1: Introduction to XML</a></li>
                <li><a href="topic2.html">Topic 2: HTML Basics</a></li>
                <li><a href="topic3.html">Topic 3: CSS Styling</a></li>
                <li><a href="topic4.html">Topic 4: JavaScript Overview</a></li>
                <li><a href="topic5.html">Topic 5: Web Design Principles</a></li>
                <li><a href="topic6.html">Topic 6: SEO Best Practices</a></li>
            </ul>
        </content>
    </index>
    
    <topic1>
        <title>Topic 1: Introduction to XML</title>
        <content>
            <p>XML (Extensible Markup Language) is a flexible text format for representing structured data. In this section, we will explore its basic syntax and structure.</p>
        </content>
    </topic1>
    
    <topic2>
        <title>Topic 2: HTML Basics</title>
        <content>
            <p>HTML (Hypertext Markup Language) is the standard language for creating web pages. Here, we'll cover the basic elements and structure of an HTML page.</p>
        </content>
    </topic2>
    
    <topic3>
        <title>Topic 3: CSS Styling</title>
        <content>
            <p>CSS (Cascading Style Sheets) is used to style and layout web pages. Learn how to change colors, fonts, and positioning in this section.</p>
        </content>
    </topic3>
    
    <topic4>
        <title>Topic 4: JavaScript Overview</title>
        <content>
            <p>JavaScript is a scripting language that allows you to create dynamic content on your website. In this section, we will introduce the basics of JavaScript.</p>
        </content>
    </topic4>
    
    <topic5>
        <title>Topic 5: Web Design Principles</title>
        <content>
            <p>Good web design is about creating intuitive, user-friendly websites. This section will discuss key principles of web design such as layout, color, and accessibility.</p>
        </content>
    </topic5>
    
    <topic6>
        <title>Topic 6: SEO Best Practices</title>
        <content>
            <p>Search Engine Optimization (SEO) is essential for making your website discoverable. In this section, we will discuss the best practices for optimizing your content for search engines.</p>
        </content>
    </topic6>
</website>
